http://www.mtiltd.ie/privacy-statement

We use a minimal set of cookies to measure traffic and provide functionality on this site. You can restrict the use of cookies on this site by changing your settings. Learn more
Settings
Accept
Cookie Settings
×
User Preference Cookie
Stores your cookie preferences
Namendti_userprefs
Persistence1 year
Stored on your device?No
Actionable?
No action required.
Google Analytics
Provides us
with anonymised visitor data
Status
Google Analytics is 										ON
Preference Stored?
NO
Actionable?
Turn off Google Analytics.
Note: requires
us to store your preference in the ndti_userprefs cookie on your machine.
Disable Google Analytics
Cookie Banner
Allows you to turn on or off the Cookie Banner
Status
Cookie Banner is 										ON
Preference Stored?
NO
Actionable?
Turn off Cookie Banner.
Note: requires
us to store your preference in the ndti_userprefs cookie on your machine.
Disable Cookie Banner
Close
Accept All Cookies
×
We need to set a Cookie on your device to remember that you've agreed to accept Cookies and remove the cookie banner. This cookie is called
ndti_userprefs.
It is set for 1 year, unless
you delete it. You can adjust your settings anytime by visiting the Cookie Policy page.
Disagree
Agree
Friday, 11 December 2020
MTI. Unit 5, Richfield Business Park, Ballycurreen, Cork, Ireland T12 V225
Toggle navigation
HomeNDT Services All ServicesIndustrial RadiographyUltrasonic TestingHygienic Tubing InspectionMagnetic Particle InspectionLiquid Pentrant InspectionFerrous Tube InspectionCorrosion under InsulationAcoustic Emission TestingRecent ProjectsCompany ProfileCompany DocumentsContact
Search
Data Privacy Notice
This is the Data Privacy Notice of the ndtireland.ie website owned by Material Test & Inspection Ltd (MTI). This document explains how we collect and process your personal data.
When you've read this, you should be able to understand how and why we collect your personal data on this website, how long we keep it and your rights with respect to any personal data that we hold.
If you have any questions, or want to exercise your rights under the GDPR, please refer to the email/physical address supplied at the end of this document.
Personal Data Collection
We collect no data that can identify you personally on our website. However, we do use cookies on this website.
Non Personal Data Collection
We use Cookies for various tasks on the website. Some of these are essential, such as functionality of our website software, but other cookies such as Google Analytics and the Cookie Banner can be turned off if you wish. All data collected by Google analytics is anonymised before it is sent to Google Ireland and cannot be used to identify you. We keep this data for 26 months. Please refer to our Cookie Policy for more details.
Your Rights under the General Data Protection Rules (GDPR)
You have the right to retrieve a copy of your personal data in machine readable format
You have the right to transfer your data to another provider
You have the right to request the removal of your data ("right to be forgotten")
You have the right to request a restriction from processing your data
You have the right to withdraw your consent to our use of your personal information at any time
You have the right to have your request dealt in 30 days of receipt
Your Rights with Respect to Personal Data
If you wish to exercise your rights please send details of your request along with 2 photocopies of recent bills (or similar) which show your name, your address and a date no later than 3 months from the date you sent your request to:
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Or by post to:
Gillian WhooleyMaterial Test & Inspection Ltd (MTI)Unit 5Richfield Business ParkBallycurreenCorkIreland
In case of a dispute you have the right to contact the Data Protection Authority, please see: https://www.dataprotection.ie
NDT Services
Industrial RadiographyUltrasonic TestingHygienic Tubing InspectionMagnetic Particle InspectionLiquid Pentrant InspectionFerrous Tube InspectionCorrosion under InsulationAcoustic Emission Testing
Latest Projects
Mercury Engineering
NDT services on Shell Corrib Gas Terminal project and Indaver Waste Management Project.
AMEC
NDT and inspection on storage tank refurbishments 20m to 86m for ConocoPhillips.
Wyeth Biopharma
Hygienic Tube testing services.
Local Weather
Cork
7°C
Partly Cloudy
Wind:
W at 11 km/h
Sat
7°C/3°C
Sun
10°C/7°C
Mon
8°C/6°C
Tue
7°C/6°C
Useful Information
Acoustic Emission AE Testing (International)Company Policies & DocumentsFind Us on LinkedInData PrivacyCookie Policy
Material Test & Inspection Ltd (MTI). Richfield Business Park, Ballycurreen, Cork, Ireland T12 V225. Tel: +353 21 4320077 Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
All text and images on this website are the property of Material Test &
Inspection Ltd and may not be used or copied without our express permission.
Back to Top
